Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1, 1.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Block to Emspak Regarding GE Organization, February 1, 1938; 10.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Emerson Organization, February 4, 1938; 11.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 7, 1938; 12.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Organization, February 11, 1938; 13.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Organization, February 11, 1938; 14.
    - Block to Matles Regarding the CIO and Inter-union Rivalry with the AFL, Including Block Letter to Edwin Norris Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and IBEW, March 3, 1938; 15.
    - Block to UE Regarding Supplies, January 16, 1939; 16.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Supplies, November 17, 1939; 17.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 18, 1939; 18.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Harry Block to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 2, 1940; 1.
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding FDR and the 1940 Elections with a Notice of Resolution for FDR, October 27, 1940; 2.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 133 Organization, November 13, 1940; 3.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, November 26, 1940; 4.
    - Block to UE Regarding Address List, November 29, 1940; 5.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Organization, December 11, 1940; 6.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding UE News, December 13, 1940; 7.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, December 20, 1940; 8.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Bonding, December 23, 1940; 9.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 115 Finances, December 23, 1940; 10.
    - Block to Local Officers and District Council Delegates Regarding Organizing Conference, January 10, 1941; 11.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Organization, January 21, 1941; 12.
    - Block to UE District 1 Presidents Regarding CIO Organization in Philadelphia, January 21, 1941; 13.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Proctor and Schwartz Mailing List, January 28, 1941; 14.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 120, January 28, 1941; 15.
    - Block to UE Regarding Supplies, January 30, 1941; 16.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 3, 1941; 17.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Wilkes-Barre Westinghouse Organization, February 7, 1941; 18.
    - Block to UE Regarding Westinghouse and General Electric, February 13, 1941; 19.
    - Block to UE Regarding Credentials, February 26, 1941; 20.
    - Block to UE Regarding UE News, February 27, 1941; 21.
    - Block to UE Regarding UE News, March 4, 1941; 22.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Local 430 with Block Letter to Local 430 Regarding Inter-union Rivalry with IBEW, March 5, 1941; 23.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding UE News, March 7, 1941; 24.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members and the Ladies Auxiliary, March 11, 1941; 25.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, March 17, 1941; 26.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 107, March 18, 1941; 27.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 18, 1941; 28.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Local 107, March 18, 1941; 29.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding the National Youth Administration, March 19, 1941; 1.
    - Block to James Matles Regarding Supplies, March 31, 1941; 2.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 10, 1941; 3.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Organization, Finances, and Locals 136 and 138, April 17, 1941; 4.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Strikes, April 21, 1941; 5.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Strikes and Staff Finances, April 22, 1941; 6.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Supplies, April 1941; 7-10.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, May 14, 1941; 11.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Supplies, May 1941; 12.
    - Block to UE Regarding Finances, June 10, 1941; 13.
    - Telegram to UE News Regarding Supplies, June 16, 1941; 14.
    - Block to UE Regarding Local 135 Contracts with Reiff and Nestor, June 19, 1941; 15.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding UE News and Local 136, June 27, 1941; 16.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Supplies, June 1941; 17.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 2, 1941; 18.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding Richardson Rubber Strike, July 10, 1941; 19.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, UE News, and Local 118, July 11, 1941; 20.
    - Block to UE Regarding Mailing List, July 24, 1941; 21.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Anti-Nazi Resolution, July 28, 1941; 22.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Jensen Manufacturing Organization in Palmyra, July 31, 1941; 23.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Supplies, July 1941; 24.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Block to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, August 8, 1941; 1.
    - Block to UE Regarding Address Change, August 8, 1941; 2.
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding 1941 Convention, August 15, 1941; 3.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, September 28, 1941; 4.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Supplies, September 1941; 5-6.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Philco Wages and Staff Members, October 6, 1941; 7.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Finances, October 15, 1941; 8.
    - Block to James Carey Regarding Staff Members, October 15, 1941; 9.
    - Block to Carey Regarding Office of Production Management, October 15, 1941; 10.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Executive Board Meeting, October 15, 1941; 11.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Radio Conference, October 15, 1941; 12.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Organization, October 15, 1941; 13.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, October 20, 1941; 14.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Radio Conference, October 24, 1941; 15.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Organization and Staff Members, October 24, 1941; 16.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Communications, November 4, 1941; 17.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Dues, Mailing List, and Local 110, November 6, 1941; 18.
    - Block to UE News Regarding Supplies, November 1941; 19.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 22, 1941; 20.
    - Block to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members, December 22, 1941; 21.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, December 22, 1941; 22.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, January 2, 1942; 1.
    - Block to James Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, January 20, 1942; 2.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, January 20, 1941; 3.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Contacts and Staff Finances, January 23, 1942; 4.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Wilmington Organization, January 25, 1942; 5.
    - Block to Matles Regarding International Resistance and Local 105, January 31, 1942; 6.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding National Child Labor Committee, February 4, 1942; 7.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Appointments, February 6, 1942; 8.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Roller Smith and SWOC, February 6, 1942; 9.
    - Block to Matles Regarding District Council Meeting, March 27, 1942; 10.
    - Block to Matles Regarding York-Lancaster Organization with Survey of Unorganized York-Lancaster Plants, March 27, 1942; 11.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, March 27, 1942; 12.
    - Block to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District Council Meeting, March 27, 1942; 13.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Racial Discrimination, March 30, 1942; 14.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Block to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, April 17, 1942; 1.
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding GE York, April 17, 1942; 2.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism with Memo on James Carey Discussion, April 17, 1942; 3.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, May 12, 1942; 4.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Production Conference, May 13, 1942; 5.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 21, 1942; 6.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding Appointment, May 28, 1942; 7.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 30, 1942; 8.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Staff Members, and Local 136, July 29, 1942; 9.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board and Factionalism, July 31, 1942; 10.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Globe Union Battery Strikes, August 21, 1942; 11.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, September 2, 1942; 12.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Finances and Factionalism, September 14, 1942; 13.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Baltimore Staff Members, October 5, 1942; 14.
    - Block to UE Regarding Supplies, October 5, 1942; 15.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Organization, November 16, 1942; 16.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Organization, November 19, 1942; 17.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Reservations, November 27, 1942; 18.
    - Block to UE Regarding Supplies, November 1942; 19.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Sunbury Westinghouse, December 11, 1942; 20.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Appointments, January 6, 1943; 1.
    - Block to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, January 11, 1943; 2.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 18, 1943; 3.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Factionalism, February 16, 1943; 4.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, February 16, 1943; 5.
    - Block to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, February 16, 1943; 6.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, February 26, 1943; 7.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, February 26, 1943; 8.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, March 2, 1943; 9.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board and Factionalism, March 4, 1943; 10.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, March 4, 1943; 11.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 4, 1943; 12.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Appointments, March 4, 1943; 13.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 11, 1943; 14.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 18, 1943; 15.
    - Block to Fitzgerald Regarding Flag Raising Ceremony, March 18, 1943; 16.
    - Block to Matles Regarding White Collar Workers and the UE News, March 19, 1943; 17.
    - Block to Fitzgerald Regarding Flag Raising Ceremony, March 31, 1943; 18.
    - Block to Matles Regarding White Collar Workers and Local 111 with April 6, 1943, Matles Memo to David Davis, March 31, 1943; 19.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, April 6, 1943; 20.
    - Block to Fitzgerald Regarding Flag Raising Ceremony with April 30, 1943, Ray Klausner Telegram to Fitzgerald Regarding Flag Raising Ceremony, April 29, 1943; 21.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding Win the War Labor Conference, July 7, 1943; 1.
    - Block to James Matles Regarding Factionalism and Bendix, July 15, 1943; 2.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Organization and CIO Local 119, July 21, 1943; 3.
    - Block to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Anti-Communism and Staff Members, July 21, 1943; 4.
    - Block to David Davis Regarding Factionalism, August 18, 1943; 5.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, September 29, 1943; 6.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 15, 1943; 7.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 140 Finances, October 20, 1943; 8.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Staff Members, October 28, 1943; 9.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 12, 1943; 10.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 112 and Factionalism, December 14, 1943; 11.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, December 21, 1943; 12.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Wages, January 14, 1944; 13.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, January 14, 1944; 14.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 135 Staff Members, January 14, 1944; 15.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 19, 1944; 16.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, January 19, 1944; 17.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, February 7, 1944; 18.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding the UE News, March 2, 1944; 19.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, March 2, 1944; 20.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding Political Aciton, April 17, 1944; 1.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and the Philadelphia School of Science and Arts, April 17, 1944; 2.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, May 1, 1944; 3.
    - Block to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Conscription, May 10, 1944; 4.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, May 19, 1944; 5.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 1, 1944; 6.
    - Block to Fitzgerald Regarding War Labor Board, June 12, 1944; 7.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Factionalism, June 15, 1944; 8.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, June 15, 1944; 9.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, August 23, 1944; 10.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding York USWA, August 23, 1944; 11.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, September 12, 1944; 12.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, September 12, 1944; 13.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding GE York Strike and Factionalism, September 12, 1944; 14.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, the War Labor Board, and Factionalism, October 27, 1944; 15.
    - Block to UE Regarding Reservations, October 27, 1944; 16.
    - Block to Ray Klausner Regarding Reservations, November 7, 1944; 17.
    - Block to UE Regarding Local 112 Finances, November 8, 1944; 18.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, November 10, 1944; 19.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and the War Labor Board, November 16, 1944; 20.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Office of Price Administration, Local 105, and Factionalism, November 27, 1944; 21.
  - General Vice President Harry Block Outgoing Correspondence, 1945-1948 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Block to Julius Emspak Regarding PAC, January 8, 1945; 1.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, January 8, 1945; 2.
    - Block to Dorothy Steffens Regarding Factionalism, January 10, 1945; 3.
    - Block to Steffens Regarding the War Labor Board and Factionalism, 4.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding War Labor Board, Local 615, and Factionalism, January 30, 1945; 5.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Dues, May 29, 1945; 6.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members and UE Conference, August 3, 1945; 7.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, August 8, 1945; 8.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 9, 1945; 9.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Mailing Lists, August 13, 1945; 10.
    - Block to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding UE Convention, August 17, 1945; 11.
    - Block to Fitzgerald Regarding UE Convention, August 23, 1945; 12.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Members, October 30, 1945; 13.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Elections of District 1 Officers, November 1, 1945; 14.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Local 101 and Philco Conference, November 23, 1945; 15.
    - Block to James Matles Regarding Wages, Locals 101 and 102, and Philco, January 11, 1946; 16.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, May 8, 1946; 17.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Mailing List, May 13, 1946; 18.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding District Council Executive Board Meeting, June 7, 1946; 19.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding District Council Executive Board Meeting, June 8, 1946; 20.
    - Block to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Members and PAC, August 6, 1946; 21.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 16, 1946; 22.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, August 29, 1946; 23.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, September 5, 1946; 24.
    - Block to Emspak Regarding 1947 Convention Proceedings, February 4, 1948; 25.
    - Block to Whom it May Concern Regarding Organization, undated; 26.
    - Telegram to Emspak Regarding Fidelity Electric and Finances, undated; 27.
  - General Vice President James Price Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, June 6, 1947; 1.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, February 16, 1949; 2.
    - William Cahn Regarding Publicity, April 14, 1947; 3.
    - Cahn Regarding Leland Stowe Broadcasts, April 16, 1947; 4.
    - Cahn Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 29, 1949; 5.
    - Fred D'Avila Regarding Publicity, June 24, 1949; 6.
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Defense Fund, November 29, 1946; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 120 and Wilmington Fibre, December 4, 1946; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, December 31, 1946; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 144, January 8, 1947; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, January 8, 1947; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with Harry Block Letters to James Matles Dated October 28 and November 4,1946, Regarding Staff Finances, January 22, 1947; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues, January 28, 1947; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 12, 1947; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues, March 12, 1947; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals, March 12, 1947; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Members, May 5, 1947; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 12, 1947; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Posters, May 26, 1947; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding CIO, June 2, 1947; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Veterans and Bower Battery, June 3, 1947; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Mailing List, June 20, 1947; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances with June 28, 1947, Paul Boylan Insurance Bill, June 1947; 23.
  - General Vice President James Price Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 9, 1947; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 30, 1947; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Committee for the Reinstatement of the 91 Discharged Allis Chalmers Workers, August 1, 1947; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, August 15, 1947; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding PAC, November 14, 1947; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Local Finances, November 20, 1947; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Defense Fund, December 8, 1947; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Area-Wide Stewards Meeting, December 15, 1947; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Meetings, December 26, 1947; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding General Metals Local 125 Strikes, January 26, 1948; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding American Jewish Labor Council, February 16, 1948; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Electric Service Manufacturing Strikes, April 15, 1948; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Publicity, May 17, 1948; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances with Receipts, June 9, 1948; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Stewards, June 21, 1948; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances with Receipt, July 29, 1948; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 136 Proctor Electric Strike, November 1, 1948; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, November 9, 1948; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 140 and 149, December 2, 1948; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Address List, March 22, 1949; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Hoover and Belmont Strikes, June 7, 1949; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, July 1, 1949; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding NLRB Elections, December 22, 1949; 23.
  - General Vice President James Price Incoming Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Federation of Greek Maritime Unions, March 20, 1950; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 138 Inter-union Rivalry with the IUE, April 12, 1950; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 109, May 8, 1950; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, July 18, 1950; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, August 18, 1950; 5.
    - Secretary of Emspak Regarding Letter, October 2, 1950; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 103, Factionalism, and Finances, August 28, 1950; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues, January 15, 1951; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, March 12, 1951; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding High Treason, April 27, 1951; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding High Treason, April 23, 1951; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 24, 1951; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, May 16, 1951; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, May 28, 1951; 14.
  - General Vice President James Price Incoming Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, June 18, 1952; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 155 Finances, June 20, 1952; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 155 Finances, June 24, 1952; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 155 Finances, September 25, 1952; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues and Finances, December 2, 1952; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 146 Dues, December 30, 1952; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 155 Finances, January 23, 1953; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 155 Finances, February 16, 1953; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 155 Finances, March 18, 1953; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 143 Finances, March 20, 1953; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 143 Finances, April 2, 1953; 11.
  - General Vice President James Price Incoming Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Shop Stewards Conference, April 7, 1947; 1.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District Constitution, May 6, 1947; 2.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District Council Meeting, May 27, 1947; 3.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District Officers, October 24, 1947; 4.
    - Ray Klausner, Secretary of Fitzgerald, Regarding Local 101, December 8, 1947; 5.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District Council Meeting, December 30, 1949; 6.
    - Gregory Kelly Regarding Workmen's Compensation, October 9, 1947; 7.
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 21, 1946; 8.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 18, 1946; 9.
    - Matles Regarding Hunt Pen Organization, January 2, 1947; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 17, 1947; 11.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 20, 1947; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 3, 1947; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Factionalism, UAW, and Local 103 Allis-Chalmers Strike with Neil Brant Letter to UE Officials Regarding Local 613 Allis-Chalmers Strike, February 4, 1947; 14.
    - Matles Regarding Reservations, February 17, 1947; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, February 18, 1947; 16.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding GE-Philadelphia Trial, February 25, 1947; 17.
  - General Vice President James Price Incoming Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 3, 1947; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Unemployment Compensation, March 4, 1947; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 5, 1947; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 14, 1947; 4.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Radio Condenser and the IBEW, April 28, 1947; 5.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Appointment, April 28, 1947; 6.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Appointments, April 29, 1947; 7.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 10, 1947; 8.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, May 14, 1947; 9.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members with Matles Letter to Francis White Regarding Organization and Matles Telegram to White Regarding Staff Members, May 19, 1947; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Allentown Western Electric, June 11, 1947; 11.